<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<newss>
<news>
    <title>UK Intellectual Property Office grants trade mark "UNBRANDED SPORTS" to UNBRANDED SPORTS
	</title>
	<content>
		London: Unbranded Sports Limited, has been granted trademark (UK00003249181) titled as ''UNBRANDED SPORTS'' from the UK Intellectual Property Office. 
		Status: Registered 
		Class/es: Class 9
		Protective helmets for sports; Protective helmets for use in sports; Helmets (Protective -) for sports; Protection helmets for sports; 
		Helmets for use in sports outh guards for sports; Mouth guards for sports use; Head guards for sports; Sports (Goggles for -);Sports (Protective helmets for -);Sports eyewear; 
		Sports glasses; Sports goggles; Sports helmets; Sports training eyeglasses; Sports training simulators; Sports' glasses.
	</content>
</news>
<news>
    <title>Field for the British Open
	</title>
	<content>
		British Open champions aged 60 or under on July 17: Zach Johnson, Rory McIlroy, Phil Mickelson, Ernie Els, Darren Clarke, Louis Oosthuizen, Padraig Harrington, Todd Hamilton, Ben Curtis, David Duval, Paul Lawrie, Mark O'Meara, Justin Leonard, Tom Lehman, John Daly, Mark Calcavecchia, Sandy Lyle.
		Top 10 and ties from the 2015 British Open: Marc Leishman, Jason Day, Jordan Spieth, Sergio Garcia, Justin Rose, Danny Willett, Jordan Niebrugge, Adam Scott.
	</content>
</news>
<news>
    <title>2016 Rio Olympics medal projections
	</title>
	<content>
		Medal projections for the 2016 Rio Olympics, compiled from predictions by the staff of The Associated Press:
		ARCHERY
		Men
		Individual
		Gold: Kim Woojin, South Korea
		Silver: Marcus D'Almeida, Brazil
		Bronze: Brady Ellison, United States
	</content>
</news>
<news>
    <title>Field for the British Open
	</title>
	<content>
		Top 50 in the world ranking from May 25: Jordan Spieth, Henrik Stenson, Bubba Watson, Justin Rose, Jason Day, Dustin Johnson, Jimmy Walker, J.B. Holmes, Hideki Matsuyama, Patrick Reed, Martin Kaymer, Chris Kirk, Matt Kuchar, Billy Horschel, Kevin Na, Bill Haas, Brooks Koepka, Ian Poulter, Lee Westwood, Jamie Donaldson, Gary Woodland, Ryan Palmer, Zach Johnson, Brandt Snedeker, Hunter Mahan, Ryan Moore, Thongchai Jaidee, Paul Casey, Branden Grace, Webb Simpson, Danny Willett, Keegan Bradley, Anirban Lahiri, Miguel Angel Jimenez, Joost Luiten, Matt Every, Bernd Wiesberger, Ben Martin, Brendon Todd.
	</content>
</news>


<news>
    <title>British Open Field
	</title>
	<content>
		SOUTHPORT, England (AP) - Players who have qualified for the 146th British Open, which starts Thursday at Royal Birkdale (players listed only in the first category for which they are eligible):
		British Open champions 60 or under on July 23: Henrik Stenson, Zach Johnson, Rory McIlroy, Phil Mickelson, Ernie Els, Darren Clarke, Louis Oosthuizen, Stewart Cink, Padraig Harrington, Todd Hamilton, David Duval, Paul Lawrie, Mark O'Meara, Justin Leonard, Tom Lehman, John Daly, Mark Calcavecchia, Sandy Lyle.
		Top 10 and ties from the 2016 British Open: J.B. Holmes, Steve Stricker, Tyrrell Hatton, Sergio Garcia, Andrew Johnston, Dustin Johnson, Soren Kjeldsen, Bill Haas.
	</content>
</news>


<news>
    <title>British Open, Tee Times
	
	</title>
	<content>
		1:32 a.m. - Mark Calcavecchia, United States; Marcel Siem, Germany; Jaco Van Zyl, South Africa.
		1:43 a.m. - Thomas Aiken, South Africa; David Lipsky, United States; Jonas Blixt, Sweden.
		1:54 a.m. - Soren Kjeldsen, Denmark; Morgan Hoffmann, United States; Danny Lee, New Zealand.
		2:05 a.m. - Richie Ramsay, Scotland; Pablo Larrazabal, Spain; Cameron Tringale, United States.
		2:16 a.m. - Steven Bowditch, Australia; Hiroshi Iwata, Japan; Ben Martin, United States.
	</content>
</news>


<news>
    <title>UK Intellectual Property Office grants trade mark "J2X" to Anthony Rowe
	</title>
	<content>
		Anthony Rowe, has been granted trademark (UK00003038598) titled as "J2X" from the UK Intellectual Property Office.
		Status: Registered
		Class/es: Class 6
		All-news sports surfacing materials (metal-);All-news sports surfacing materials (metal-) for indoor use;All-news sports surfacing materials for (metal-) outdoor use.
	</content>
</news>


<news>
    <title>United Kingdom Intellectual Property Office Publishes Application for Trademark "J2X" to Anthony Rowe for Multiple Goods
	</title>
	<content>
		The trademark application (journal number: 2014/007) was published on Feb. 14. The description of the mark registered is: "All-news sports surfacing materials (metal-);All-news sports surfacing materials (metal-) for indoor use;All-news sports surfacing materials for (metal-) outdoor use. Sports eyewear;Sports glasses;Sports helmets;Protection helmets for sports;Abdomen protectors for protection against injury [other than parts of sports suits or adapted for use in specific sporting activities];Elbow protectors (protective-) for use against accidents [other than sports articles];Shin guards for protection against injury [other than sports articles or parts of sports suits];
	</content>
</news>


<news>
    <title>United Kingdom Intellectual Property Office Publishes Application for Trademark "DBA" to Storm TRENTHAM for Multiple Goods and Services
	</title>
	<content>
		The trademark application (journal number: 2013/037) was published on Sept. 13. The description of the mark registered is: "Clothing; footwear; headgear; undergarments. Agency services for promoting sports people; business management of sports people and facilities; business management of sports people; promoting the goods and services of others by arranging for sponsors to affiliate their goods and services with an awards program, a sports competition and sporting activities; promotion of sports competitions, cultural activities, entertainment events and sports events; promotional management for sports people; advisory and consultancy services relating to the aforesaid.
	</content>
</news>


<news>
    <title>UK Intellectual Property Office grants trade mark "FXR Sports/FXR Sports" to WELLGOOD ONLINE LTD	
	</title>
	<content>
		DATELINE: Lahore 
		London: WELLGOOD ONLINE LTD, has been granted trademark (UK00003121628) titled as "FXR Sports/FXR Sports" from the UK Intellectual Property Office.
		Status: Registered
	</content>
</news>


<news>
    <title>U.S. Women's Open Tee Times
	</title>
	<content>
		July 13-16
		At Trump National Golf Course
		Bedminster, N.J.
		All Times EDT
		(a-amateur)
		Thursday-Friday
		First Hole-10th Hole
		6:45 a.m.- 12:30 p.m. - Casey Danielson, Osceola, Wis.; Jessica Welch, Thomasville, Ga.; (a) SoWhi Kang, South Korea
		6:56 a.m.-12:41 p.m. - Elin Arvidsson, Sweden; (a) Brooke Seay, Rancho Santa Fe, Calif.; Angel Yin, Arcadia, Calif.
	</content>
</news>


<news>
    <title>Adrian Peterson active for the Vikings against Lions
	</title>
	<content>
		Adrian Peterson is active for the Minnesota Vikings against Detroit after being listed as questionable because of an illness.
		In Kansas City, Steelers quarterback Landry Jones is making his first NFL start because Ben Roethlisberger and Michael Vick are inactive. Chiefs wide receiver Jeremy Maclin is inactive because of a concussion.
	</content>
</news>


<news>
    <title>UK Intellectual Property Office grants trade mark "Air Rush" to Steven Richardsen
	</title>
	<content>
		London: Steven Richardsen, has been granted trademark (UK00003168368) titled as "Air Rush" from the UK Intellectual Property Office.
	</content>
</news>


<news>
    <title>Baseball Capsules
	</title>
	<content>
		NEW YORK (AP) - Michael Pineda struck out a career-high 16 batters in seven dominant innings as the New York Yankees downed the Baltimore Orioles 6-2.
		Pineda (5-0) matched David Cone and David Wells for the second-most strikeouts in a game by a Yankees pitcher. Ron Guidry fanned 18 in 1978.
		The 16 strikeouts were the most by the Orioles against one pitcher in a nine-inning game, according to STATS. Baltimore struck out against 18 times overall, a club record for a nine-inning game.
	</content>
</news>


<news>
    <title>Medalists projected by AP at the Sochi Olympics
	</title>
	<content>
		SOCHI, Russia (AP) - A list of medalists projected by The Associated Press for the Sochi Olympics:
		ALPINE SKIING
		Men
		Downhill
		Gold - Aksel Lund Svindal, Norway
		Silver - Bode Miller, United States
		Bronze - Adrien Theaux, France
		Super-G
	</content>
</news>


<news>
    <title>UK Intellectual Property Office grants trade mark "GB Taekwondo" to Sport Taekwondo UK Ltd
	</title>
	<content>
		London: Sport Taekwondo UK Ltd, has been granted trademark (UK00003209224) titled as "GB Taekwondo" from the UK Intellectual Property Office.
	</content>
</news>
<news>
    <title>news forecast: Air pollution: Summary: Lighting up: High tides:news report: Around the UK and Ireland: UK and Ireland Noon: Sun Rain Temp (deg. C) news hrs mm High/Low (noon): Sun Rain Temp (deg. C) news hrs mm High/Low (noon): Sun and Moon: Around the world: UK and Ireland Five day forecast: Atlantic front Noon today: deg. C deg. F news: deg. C deg. F news:deg. C deg. F news: deg. C deg. F news
	</title>
    <content>  London, SE England, E Anglia, Lincolnshire A misty start, then remaining dull with plenty of low cloud. Gentle westerly winds. Max temp 5-8C (41-46F). Tonight, misty. Min temp 2-5C (36-41F).
			NW England, Yorkshire, NE England, Northern Ireland After early rain clears, it will be dry with some sunshine developing, mainly in the east. Gentle westerly winds. Max temp 5-8C (41-46F). Tonight, misty. Min temp 1-4C (34-39F).
			Cent S England, SW England, Channel Is, Wales, E Midlands, W Midlands, Ireland A dull and misty start. Then, rather a lot of cloud, but also some sunshine developing, more especially to the lee of high ground. Light south-westerly winds. Max temp 7-10C (45-50F). Tonight, damp and misty. Min temp 2-5C (36-41F).
			W Scotland, SE Scotland Early cloud and showers in the south. Bright and dry with spells of sunshine later. Light westerly winds. Max temp 5-8C (41-46F). Tonight, mist and fog. Min temp 0-3C (32-37F).
			NW Scotland, NE Scotland, W Isles It looks set to be a mostly dry day with plenty of sunshine in many places. A few mist patches lingering around the Highlands. Moderate westerly winds. Max temp 5-8C (41-46F). Tonight, mist and fog. Min temp -3 to 0C (27-32F).				N Isles Early showers in Shetland. Then, mostly fine and dry with plenty of sun and little cloud. Moderate westerly winds. Max temp 6-9C (43-48F). Tonight, clear. Min temp 2-5C (36-41F).
	</content>
</news>


<news>
    <title>These are the school snow closures in Surrey for Friday March 2; 
		Most schools are expecting to re-open after the weekend
	</title>
	<content>
		Schools in several parts of Surrey have announced closuresthis week due tosnowfall brought to the UK by the so-called 'Beast from the East'.
		TheSurrey County Councilwebsite publishes details of school closures as they are announced.
		Here we have listed the schools that have confirmed they will be closed on Friday (March 2) - and their anticipated reopening date, if known - asfurther snowy news is expected across the county.
	</content>
</news>


<news>
    <title>Red Flag Warning Issued by NWS Omaha (Eastern Nebraska and Southeastern Iowa - Omaha Valley)
	</title>
	<content>
		National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration has issued the following news alert:

Event: Red Flag Warning
Alert:

...RED FLAG WARNING IN EFFECT UNTIL 7 PM... 

.HIGH TEMPERATURES WILL REACH THE MID TO UPPER 70S TODAY...WITH 
DEWPOINTS FALLING INTO THE 20S...RESULTING IN RELATIVE HUMIDITY IN 
THE TEENS TO AROUND 20 PERCENT. ALSO...SOUTHWEST WINDS WILL REACH 
15 TO 25 MPH TODAY...WITH HIGHER GUSTS. GIVEN THE DRY GROUND 
CONDITIONS...THE POTENTIAL TODAY IS HIGH FOR EXTREME FIRE 
BEHAVIOR.
	</content>
</news>


<news>
    <title>Global Automatic news Stations Market By Analysis and Forecasts by Types, Technologies and Application
	</title>
	<content>
		India, Feb. 13 -- ?The recently published report titled?Global Automatic news StationsIndustry 2018 Market Research Report is an in depth study providing complete analysis of the industry for the period 2018 2025. It provides complete overview of Global Automatic news Stations Market considering all the major industry trends, market dynamics and competitive scenario.TheGlobal Automatic news StationsIndustry Report 2018is an in depth study analyzing the current state of the Global Automatic news Stations Market. It provides brief overview of the market focusing on definitions, market segmentation, end-use applications and industry chain analysis.
	</content>
</news>


<news>
    <title>news.com(R) Reigns as Most Trusted Source of Online news Information in Recent Study Conducted by Nielsen Media Research 
	</title>
	<content>
		ATLANTA, Dec. 15 /PRNewswire/ -- A study conducted by Nielsen Media Research confirms what usage numbers have indicated for years -- news.com, the Web site of The news Channel(R), is the most trusted source of news information on the Web.
	</content>
</news>


<news>
    <title>Feature: news derivatives
	</title>
	<content>
		news derivatives emerged in the mid 1990s, evolving out of insurance derivatives and the alternative risk transfer market. news derivatives are an important instrument as their structures seek to manage volume risk rather than pure price risk. They are also interesting as the underlying is not directly tradeable.
		In this paper the economics of news risk, including the impact on earnings and the key characteristics of news risk products, are outlined. In part 2, the major types of news risk derivatives are identified. In part 3, the pricing of news derivatives is examined.
	</content>
</news>


<news>
    <title>The news Channel Puts the news in Your Pocket; Popular Source of news Information Takes The Wireless Arena By Storm
	</title>
	<content>
		Through its news Anywhere Services the site provides specialized news information to consumers through various wireless devices such as cellular phones, pagers, and Personal Digital Assistants. Users can register for Wireless news directly on The news Channel Web site, www.news.com, or can access news information through one of the company's many wireless partners. The news Channel is the news provider for companies such as Verizon Wireless, ATT Wireless, Sprint PCS, Palm, Nokia and AvantGo.
	</content>
</news>


<news>
    <title>The news Channel(R) Showcases New Screensaver With news-Triggered Images; 
		Users Receive Glanceable news Update and Gallery of User-Submitted news Photos 
	</title>
	<content>
		Using patent-pending technology, the new screensaver, which can be downloaded free of charge at http://www.news.com/photogallery , showcases a rotating gallery of awe-inspiring news photos, all of which were submitted by news.com(R) users. These lush images, highlighting news scenes from communities around the United States, are also part of the site's popular Photo Gallery. The photos automatically change along with local news conditions -- which are also constantly displayed on the user's screen when the screensaver is active.
	</content>
</news>


<news>
    <title>news Channel Acquiring news Underground
	</title>
	<content>
		The news Channel Companies is acquiring the news Underground, giving the news Channel - already by far the most-visited news news Web site in the United States - an even greater lead over other such companies.
		The news Channel Companies is going to gobble up one of its top competitors, the news Underground.
		The acquisition, announced on Monday afternoon, will give the news Channel - already by far the most-
	</content>
</news>


<news>
    <title>New news.com Provides Users Easy Access to More Localized news; 
		The news Channel Announces Redesign of Top Online news Site news.com	
	</title>
	<content>
		The news Channel® (TWC) announces a redesign of its popular website news.com , offering consumers an updated, user-centered experience available July 15. Its first major redesign in 10 years, the new news.com introduces a fresh, modern design and includes options for consumers to create a more customized news experience. As a result of extensive consumer research, new features include a more intuitive navigation; more localized news specific to addresses and places of interest; saved locations visible from every page on the site; integrated user-generated content through iWitness news; and customizable apps.
	</content>
</news>


<news>
    <title>news Underground Introduces news WebCam Feature 
	</title>
	<content>
		"With the launch of our news WunderCam feature, we hope to encourage our large community of users, who share personal news station data, to add their webcams to our online network," said Alan Steremberg, president and co-founder of news Underground. "With daily animations and news visuals, the webcam feature offers users a new perspective on news reporting, beyond traditional news data consisting of numbers and text. By offering links to personal news webcams, we will enable our community to capture unique and exciting news footage."
	</content>
</news>


<news>
    <title>Fire news Watch Issued by NWS Dodge City (Southwestern Kansas)
	</title>
	<content>
		Washington: National news Service has issued the following alert:

		Fire news Watch
		Alert: 

		...FIRE news WATCH IN EFFECT THURSDAY AFTERNOON FOR WIND AND
		LOW RELATIVE HUMIDITY FOR FIRE news ZONES 030...031...043...044...
	</content>
</news>


<news>
    <title>US hits record for news disasters
	</title>
	<content>The US had 16 news disasters last year with damage exceeding a billion dollars, the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration (NOAA) said yesterday. That ties 2011 for the number of billion-dollar disasters, but the total cost blew past the previous record of US$215b, set in 2005.
		Costs are adjusted for inflation, and NOAA keeps track of billion- dollar news disasters going back to 1980.
	</content>
</news>


<news>
    <title>US hits record for costly news disasters: $306 billion
	</title>
	<content>
		With three strong hurricanes, wildfires, hail, flooding, tornadoes and drought, the United States tallied a record high bill last year for news disasters: $306 billion.
		The U.S. had 16disasterslast year with damage exceeding a billion dollars, the National Oceanic and AtmosphericAdministrationsaid Monday. That ties 2011 for the number of billion-dollar disasters, but the total cost blew past the previous record of $215 billion in 2005.
		Costs are adjusted for inflation and NOAA keeps track of billion-dollar news disasters going back to 190.
		Three of the five most expensive hurricanes in U.S. history hit last year.
	</content>
</news>


<news>
    <title>Map shows news disasters across state
	</title>
	<content>
		The report, released by advocacy group Environment Minnesota, includes a clickable online map showing 82 of Minnesota's 87 counties have sustained federally declared news disasters since 2007. Those disasters including flooding, tornadoes and severe storms. Only Koochiching County in far north-central Minnesota, and Todd, Morrison, Benton and Sherburne counties in central Minnesota stayed off the federal disaster lists in that five-year period.
	</content>
</news>


<news>
    <title>BRIEF: news and Disaster Preparedness Day Saturday at the mall
	</title>
	<content>
		Mike Honigsberg, director of Enid and Garfield County Emergency Management, said the event is free and will include drawings throughout the event for NOAA news radios.
		"Come see us and many other responders that work hard to protect and serve you all," he said. "There will be a static display of emergency vehicles and inside we'll have several organizations represented. So come out and talk to us."
		With severe news season under way, news and Disaster Preparedness Day is a way for the public to get educated on what they need to do when severe news strikes. The day also gives the public a chance to speak with a number of emergency response agency officials and ask questions.
	</content>
</news>


<news>
    <title>Mayor declares news disaster
	</title>
	<content>
		The disaster declaration was signed Monday by Mayor John Tyler Hammons after the area was hit with a blizzard last week.
		Disasters were also declared after ice storms hit the area in 2007 and 2008, Moore said.
		The declaration for the blizzard of 2009 will have no effect unless the president issues a disaster declaration for the state, which will likely be in the next two weeks if it happens, Moore said.
		Whether the presidential declaration is issued depends on the amount of damage statewide, said Jeff Smith, Muskogee County Emergency Management director. For the state declaration, damage would have to total about $4 million.
	</content>
</news>


<news>
    <title>Brace yourself for a scorcher: 2015 set to be warmest on record, warn climate scientists
	</title>
	<content>
		This interactive graphic above created by Nasa, shows how the Earth has changed over time (credit: Nasa)
		However, there are expectations that while 2015 will become the warmest year on record, much of that may be due to the unseasonable El Nino event rather than a rapid acceleration in climate change.
		Others have also expressed doubts over the reliability of global temperature data.
		In April, London-based think tank, the Global Warming Policy Foundation, announced it was launching an inquiry into the integrity of official surface temperature records.
	</content>
</news>


<news>
    <title>The strength and quality of climate perceptions
	</title>
	<content>
		An organization's climate is a valuable resource for organizational effectiveness because it influences employees' commitment to the organization (e.g. [5] Carr et al. , 2003). However, research has shown that individual climate perceptions may vary among group members who share a similar environment (e.g. [14] Klein et al. , 2001). Employees may perceive their environment differently because they "draw on what they experience as their own backgrounds, their 'selves' when making sense of organizational events" ([20] Peterson and Smith, 2000, p. 110). Additionally, employees may develop different climate perceptions in weak organizational environments. In weak, as opposed to strong, organizational environments, there are ambiguous organizational values and few behavioral norms (e.g. [17] Mischel, 1977), which allows for individual differences in expectations and perceptions. The extent to which group members differ in their climate perceptions has been referred to as climate strength.
	</content>
</news>


<news>
    <title>Dramatic Climate Change Is Unpredictable
	</title>
	<content>
		The fear that global temperature can change very quickly and cause dramatic climate changes that may have a disastrous impact on many countries and populations is great around the world. But what causes climate change and is it possible to predict future climate change? New research from the Niels Bohr Institute at the University of Copenhagen shows that it may be due to an accumulation of different chaotic influences and as a result would be difficult to predict. The results have just been published in Geophysical Research Letters.
	</content>
</news>
</newss>