<weather>
    <title>UK Intellectual Property Office grants trade mark "UNBRANDED SPORTS" to UNBRANDED SPORTS
	</title>
	<content>
		London: Unbranded Sports Limited, has been granted trademark (UK00003249181) titled as ''UNBRANDED SPORTS'' from the UK Intellectual Property Office. 
		Status: Registered 
		Class/es: Class 9
		Protective helmets for sports; Protective helmets for use in sports; Helmets (Protective -) for sports; Protection helmets for sports; 
		Helmets for use in sports outh guards for sports; Mouth guards for sports use; Head guards for sports; Sports (Goggles for -);Sports (Protective helmets for -);Sports eyewear; 
		Sports glasses; Sports goggles; Sports helmets; Sports training eyeglasses; Sports training simulators; Sports' glasses.
	</content>
</weather>


<weather>
    <title>Field for the British Open
	</title>
	<content>
		British Open champions aged 60 or under on July 17: Zach Johnson, Rory McIlroy, Phil Mickelson, Ernie Els, Darren Clarke, Louis Oosthuizen, Padraig Harrington, Todd Hamilton, Ben Curtis, David Duval, Paul Lawrie, Mark O'Meara, Justin Leonard, Tom Lehman, John Daly, Mark Calcavecchia, Sandy Lyle.
		Top 10 and ties from the 2015 British Open: Marc Leishman, Jason Day, Jordan Spieth, Sergio Garcia, Justin Rose, Danny Willett, Jordan Niebrugge, Adam Scott.
	</content>
</weather>


<weather>
    <title>2016 Rio Olympics medal projections
	
	</title>
	<content>
		Medal projections for the 2016 Rio Olympics, compiled from predictions by the staff of The Associated Press:
		ARCHERY
		Men
		Individual
		Gold: Kim Woojin, South Korea
		Silver: Marcus D'Almeida, Brazil
		Bronze: Brady Ellison, United States
	</content>
</weather>


<weather>
    <title>Field for the British Open
	</title>
	<content>
		Top 50 in the world ranking from May 25: Jordan Spieth, Henrik Stenson, Bubba Watson, Justin Rose, Jason Day, Dustin Johnson, Jimmy Walker, J.B. Holmes, Hideki Matsuyama, Patrick Reed, Martin Kaymer, Chris Kirk, Matt Kuchar, Billy Horschel, Kevin Na, Bill Haas, Brooks Koepka, Ian Poulter, Lee Westwood, Jamie Donaldson, Gary Woodland, Ryan Palmer, Zach Johnson, Brandt Snedeker, Hunter Mahan, Ryan Moore, Thongchai Jaidee, Paul Casey, Branden Grace, Webb Simpson, Danny Willett, Keegan Bradley, Anirban Lahiri, Miguel Angel Jimenez, Joost Luiten, Matt Every, Bernd Wiesberger, Ben Martin, Brendon Todd.
	</content>
</weather>


<weather>
    <title>British Open Field
	</title>
	<content>
		SOUTHPORT, England (AP) - Players who have qualified for the 146th British Open, which starts Thursday at Royal Birkdale (players listed only in the first category for which they are eligible):
		British Open champions 60 or under on July 23: Henrik Stenson, Zach Johnson, Rory McIlroy, Phil Mickelson, Ernie Els, Darren Clarke, Louis Oosthuizen, Stewart Cink, Padraig Harrington, Todd Hamilton, David Duval, Paul Lawrie, Mark O'Meara, Justin Leonard, Tom Lehman, John Daly, Mark Calcavecchia, Sandy Lyle.
		Top 10 and ties from the 2016 British Open: J.B. Holmes, Steve Stricker, Tyrrell Hatton, Sergio Garcia, Andrew Johnston, Dustin Johnson, Soren Kjeldsen, Bill Haas.
	</content>
</weather>


<weather>
    <title>British Open, Tee Times
	
	</title>
	<content>
		1:32 a.m. - Mark Calcavecchia, United States; Marcel Siem, Germany; Jaco Van Zyl, South Africa.
		1:43 a.m. - Thomas Aiken, South Africa; David Lipsky, United States; Jonas Blixt, Sweden.
		1:54 a.m. - Soren Kjeldsen, Denmark; Morgan Hoffmann, United States; Danny Lee, New Zealand.
		2:05 a.m. - Richie Ramsay, Scotland; Pablo Larrazabal, Spain; Cameron Tringale, United States.
		2:16 a.m. - Steven Bowditch, Australia; Hiroshi Iwata, Japan; Ben Martin, United States.
	</content>
</weather>


<weather>
    <title>UK Intellectual Property Office grants trade mark "J2X" to Anthony Rowe
	</title>
	<content>
		Anthony Rowe, has been granted trademark (UK00003038598) titled as "J2X" from the UK Intellectual Property Office.
		Status: Registered
		Class/es: Class 6
		All-weather sports surfacing materials (metal-);All-weather sports surfacing materials (metal-) for indoor use;All-weather sports surfacing materials for (metal-) outdoor use.
	</content>
</weather>


<weather>
    <title>United Kingdom Intellectual Property Office Publishes Application for Trademark "J2X" to Anthony Rowe for Multiple Goods
	</title>
	<content>
		The trademark application (journal number: 2014/007) was published on Feb. 14. The description of the mark registered is: "All-weather sports surfacing materials (metal-);All-weather sports surfacing materials (metal-) for indoor use;All-weather sports surfacing materials for (metal-) outdoor use. Sports eyewear;Sports glasses;Sports helmets;Protection helmets for sports;Abdomen protectors for protection against injury [other than parts of sports suits or adapted for use in specific sporting activities];Elbow protectors (protective-) for use against accidents [other than sports articles];Shin guards for protection against injury [other than sports articles or parts of sports suits];
	</content>
</weather>


<weather>
    <title>United Kingdom Intellectual Property Office Publishes Application for Trademark "DBA" to Storm TRENTHAM for Multiple Goods and Services
	</title>
	<content>
		The trademark application (journal number: 2013/037) was published on Sept. 13. The description of the mark registered is: "Clothing; footwear; headgear; undergarments. Agency services for promoting sports people; business management of sports people and facilities; business management of sports people; promoting the goods and services of others by arranging for sponsors to affiliate their goods and services with an awards program, a sports competition and sporting activities; promotion of sports competitions, cultural activities, entertainment events and sports events; promotional management for sports people; advisory and consultancy services relating to the aforesaid.
	</content>
</weather>


<weather>
    <title>UK Intellectual Property Office grants trade mark "FXR Sports/FXR Sports" to WELLGOOD ONLINE LTD	
	</title>
	<content>
		DATELINE: Lahore 
		London: WELLGOOD ONLINE LTD, has been granted trademark (UK00003121628) titled as "FXR Sports/FXR Sports" from the UK Intellectual Property Office.
		Status: Registered
	</content>
</weather>


<weather>
    <title>U.S. Women's Open Tee Times
	</title>
	<content>
		July 13-16
		At Trump National Golf Course
		Bedminster, N.J.
		All Times EDT
		(a-amateur)
		Thursday-Friday
		First Hole-10th Hole
		6:45 a.m.- 12:30 p.m. - Casey Danielson, Osceola, Wis.; Jessica Welch, Thomasville, Ga.; (a) SoWhi Kang, South Korea
		6:56 a.m.-12:41 p.m. - Elin Arvidsson, Sweden; (a) Brooke Seay, Rancho Santa Fe, Calif.; Angel Yin, Arcadia, Calif.
	</content>
</weather>


<weather>
    <title>Adrian Peterson active for the Vikings against Lions
	</title>
	<content>
		Adrian Peterson is active for the Minnesota Vikings against Detroit after being listed as questionable because of an illness.
		In Kansas City, Steelers quarterback Landry Jones is making his first NFL start because Ben Roethlisberger and Michael Vick are inactive. Chiefs wide receiver Jeremy Maclin is inactive because of a concussion.
	</content>
</weather>


<weather>
    <title>UK Intellectual Property Office grants trade mark "Air Rush" to Steven Richardsen
	</title>
	<content>
		London: Steven Richardsen, has been granted trademark (UK00003168368) titled as "Air Rush" from the UK Intellectual Property Office.
	</content>
</weather>


<weather>
    <title>Baseball Capsules
	</title>
	<content>
		NEW YORK (AP) - Michael Pineda struck out a career-high 16 batters in seven dominant innings as the New York Yankees downed the Baltimore Orioles 6-2.
		Pineda (5-0) matched David Cone and David Wells for the second-most strikeouts in a game by a Yankees pitcher. Ron Guidry fanned 18 in 1978.
		The 16 strikeouts were the most by the Orioles against one pitcher in a nine-inning game, according to STATS. Baltimore struck out against 18 times overall, a club record for a nine-inning game.
	</content>
</weather>


<weather>
    <title>Medalists projected by AP at the Sochi Olympics
	</title>
	<content>
		SOCHI, Russia (AP) - A list of medalists projected by The Associated Press for the Sochi Olympics:
		ALPINE SKIING
		Men
		Downhill
		Gold - Aksel Lund Svindal, Norway
		Silver - Bode Miller, United States
		Bronze - Adrien Theaux, France
		Super-G
	</content>
</weather>


<weather>
    <title>UK Intellectual Property Office grants trade mark "GB Taekwondo" to Sport Taekwondo UK Ltd
	</title>
	<content>
		London: Sport Taekwondo UK Ltd, has been granted trademark (UK00003209224) titled as "GB Taekwondo" from the UK Intellectual Property Office.
	</content>
</weather>