<weather>
    <title>Weather forecast: Air pollution: Summary: Lighting up: High tides:Weather report: Around the UK and Ireland: UK and Ireland Noon: Sun Rain Temp (deg. C) Weather hrs mm High/Low (noon): Sun Rain Temp (deg. C) Weather hrs mm High/Low (noon): Sun & Moon: Around the world: UK and Ireland Five day forecast: Atlantic front Noon today: deg. C deg. F Weather: deg. C deg. F Weather:deg. C deg. F Weather: deg. C deg. F Weather
	</title>
    <content>  London, SE England, E Anglia, Lincolnshire A misty start, then remaining dull with plenty of low cloud. Gentle westerly winds. Max temp 5-8C (41-46F). Tonight, misty. Min temp 2-5C (36-41F).
			NW England, Yorkshire, NE England, Northern Ireland After early rain clears, it will be dry with some sunshine developing, mainly in the east. Gentle westerly winds. Max temp 5-8C (41-46F). Tonight, misty. Min temp 1-4C (34-39F).
			Cent S England, SW England, Channel Is, Wales, E Midlands, W Midlands, Ireland A dull and misty start. Then, rather a lot of cloud, but also some sunshine developing, more especially to the lee of high ground. Light south-westerly winds. Max temp 7-10C (45-50F). Tonight, damp and misty. Min temp 2-5C (36-41F).
			W Scotland, SE Scotland Early cloud and showers in the south. Bright and dry with spells of sunshine later. Light westerly winds. Max temp 5-8C (41-46F). Tonight, mist and fog. Min temp 0-3C (32-37F).
			NW Scotland, NE Scotland, W Isles It looks set to be a mostly dry day with plenty of sunshine in many places. A few mist patches lingering around the Highlands. Moderate westerly winds. Max temp 5-8C (41-46F). Tonight, mist and fog. Min temp -3 to 0C (27-32F).				N Isles Early showers in Shetland. Then, mostly fine and dry with plenty of sun and little cloud. Moderate westerly winds. Max temp 6-9C (43-48F). Tonight, clear. Min temp 2-5C (36-41F).
	</content>
</weather>


<weather>
    <title>These are the school snow closures in Surrey for Friday March 2; 
		Most schools are expecting to re-open after the weekend
	</title>
	<content>
		Schools in several parts of Surrey have announced closuresthis week due tosnowfall brought to the UK by the so-called 'Beast from the East'.
		TheSurrey County Councilwebsite publishes details of school closures as they are announced.
		Here we have listed the schools that have confirmed they will be closed on Friday (March 2) - and their anticipated reopening date, if known - asfurther snowy weather is expected across the county.
	</content>
</weather>


<weather>
    <title>Red Flag Warning Issued by NWS Omaha (Eastern Nebraska and Southeastern Iowa - Omaha Valley)
	</title>
	<content>
		National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration has issued the following weather alert:

Event: Red Flag Warning
Alert:

...RED FLAG WARNING IN EFFECT UNTIL 7 PM... 

.HIGH TEMPERATURES WILL REACH THE MID TO UPPER 70S TODAY...WITH 
DEWPOINTS FALLING INTO THE 20S...RESULTING IN RELATIVE HUMIDITY IN 
THE TEENS TO AROUND 20 PERCENT. ALSO...SOUTHWEST WINDS WILL REACH 
15 TO 25 MPH TODAY...WITH HIGHER GUSTS. GIVEN THE DRY GROUND 
CONDITIONS...THE POTENTIAL TODAY IS HIGH FOR EXTREME FIRE 
BEHAVIOR.
	</content>
</weather>


<weather>
    <title>Global Automatic Weather Stations Market By Analysis and Forecasts by Types, Technologies and Application
	</title>
	<content>
		India, Feb. 13 -- ?The recently published report titled?Global Automatic Weather StationsIndustry 2018 Market Research Reportis an in depth study providing complete analysis of the industry for the period 2018 2025. It provides complete overview of Global Automatic Weather Stations Market considering all the major industry trends, market dynamics and competitive scenario.TheGlobal Automatic Weather StationsIndustry Report 2018is an in depth study analyzing the current state of the Global Automatic Weather Stations Market. It provides brief overview of the market focusing on definitions, market segmentation, end-use applications and industry chain analysis.
	</content>
</weather>


<weather>
    <title>weather.com(R) Reigns as Most Trusted Source of Online Weather Information in Recent Study Conducted by Nielsen Media Research 
	</title>
	<content>
		ATLANTA, Dec. 15 /PRNewswire/ -- A study conducted by Nielsen Media Research confirms what usage numbers have indicated for years -- weather.com, the Web site of The Weather Channel(R), is the most trusted source of weather information on the Web.
	</content>
</weather>


<weather>
    <title>Feature: Weather derivatives
	</title>
	<content>
		Weather derivatives emerged in the mid 1990s, evolving out of insurance derivatives and the alternative risk transfer market. Weather derivatives are an important instrument as their structures seek to manage volume risk rather than pure price risk. They are also interesting as the underlying is not directly tradeable.
		In this paper the economics of weather risk, including the impact on earnings and the key characteristics of weather risk products, are outlined. In part 2, the major types of weather risk derivatives are identified. In part 3, the pricing of weather derivatives is examined.
	</content>
</weather>


<weather>
    <title>The Weather Channel Puts the Weather in Your Pocket; Popular Source of Weather Information Takes The Wireless Arena By Storm
	</title>
	<content>
		Through its Weather Anywhere Services the site provides specialized weather information to consumers through various wireless devices such as cellular phones, pagers, and Personal Digital Assistants. Users can register for Wireless Weather directly on The Weather Channel Web site, www.weather.com, or can access weather information through one of the company's many wireless partners. The Weather Channel is the weather provider for companies such as Verizon Wireless, AT&T Wireless, Sprint PCS, Palm, Nokia and AvantGo.
	</content>
</weather>


<weather>
    <title>The Weather Channel(R) Showcases New Screensaver With Weather-Triggered Images; 
		Users Receive Glanceable Weather Update and Gallery of User-Submitted Weather Photos 
	</title>
	<content>
		Using patent-pending technology, the new screensaver, which can be downloaded free of charge at http://www.weather.com/photogallery , showcases a rotating gallery of awe-inspiring weather photos, all of which were submitted by weather.com(R) users. These lush images, highlighting weather scenes from communities around the United States, are also part of the site's popular Photo Gallery. The photos automatically change along with local weather conditions -- which are also constantly displayed on the user's screen when the screensaver is active.
	</content>
</weather>


<weather>
    <title>Weather Channel Acquiring Weather Underground
	</title>
	<content>
		The Weather Channel Companies is acquiring the Weather Underground, giving the Weather Channel - already by far the most-visited weather news Web site in the United States - an even greater lead over other such companies.
		The Weather Channel Companies is going to gobble up one of its top competitors, the Weather Underground.
		The acquisition, announced on Monday afternoon, will give the Weather Channel - already by far the most-
	</content>
</weather>


<weather>
    <title>New weather.com Provides Users Easy Access to More Localized Weather; 
		The Weather Channel Announces Redesign of Top Online Weather Site weather.com	
	</title>
	<content>
		The Weather Channel® (TWC) announces a redesign of its popular website weather.com , offering consumers an updated, user-centered experience available July 15. Its first major redesign in 10 years, the new weather.com introduces a fresh, modern design and includes options for consumers to create a more customized weather experience. As a result of extensive consumer research, new features include a more intuitive navigation; more localized weather specific to addresses and places of interest; saved locations visible from every page on the site; integrated user-generated content through iWitness Weather; and customizable apps.
	</content>
</weather>


<weather>
    <title>Weather Underground Introduces Weather WebCam Feature 
	</title>
	<content>
		"With the launch of our weather WunderCam feature, we hope to encourage our large community of users, who share personal weather station data, to add their webcams to our online network," said Alan Steremberg, president and co-founder of Weather Underground. "With daily animations and weather visuals, the webcam feature offers users a new perspective on weather reporting, beyond traditional weather data consisting of numbers and text. By offering links to personal weather webcams, we will enable our community to capture unique and exciting weather footage."
	</content>
</weather>


<weather>
    <title>Fire Weather Watch Issued by NWS Dodge City (Southwestern Kansas)
	</title>
	<content>
		Washington: National Weather Service has issued the following alert:

		Fire Weather Watch
		Alert: 

		...FIRE WEATHER WATCH IN EFFECT THURSDAY AFTERNOON FOR WIND AND
		LOW RELATIVE HUMIDITY FOR FIRE WEATHER ZONES 030...031...043...044...
	</content>
</weather>


<weather>
    <title>US hits record for weather disasters
	</title>
	<content>The US had 16 weather disasters last year with damage exceeding a billion dollars, the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration (NOAA) said yesterday. That ties 2011 for the number of billion-dollar disasters, but the total cost blew past the previous record of US$215b, set in 2005.
		Costs are adjusted for inflation, and NOAA keeps track of billion- dollar weather disasters going back to 1980.
	</content>
</weather>


<weather>
    <title>US hits record for costly weather disasters: $306 billion
	</title>
	<content>
		With three strong hurricanes, wildfires, hail, flooding, tornadoes and drought, the United States tallied a record high bill last year for weather disasters: $306 billion.
		The U.S. had 16disasterslast year with damage exceeding a billion dollars, the National Oceanic and AtmosphericAdministrationsaid Monday. That ties 2011 for the number of billion-dollar disasters, but the total cost blew past the previous record of $215 billion in 2005.
		Costs are adjusted for inflation and NOAA keeps track of billion-dollar weather disasters going back to 190.
		Three of the five most expensive hurricanes in U.S. history hit last year.
	</content>
</weather>


<weather>
    <title>Map shows weather disasters across state
	</title>
	<content>
		The report, released by advocacy group Environment Minnesota, includes a clickable online map showing 82 of Minnesota's 87 counties have sustained federally declared weather disasters since 2007. Those disasters including flooding, tornadoes and severe storms. Only Koochiching County in far north-central Minnesota, and Todd, Morrison, Benton and Sherburne counties in central Minnesota stayed off the federal disaster lists in that five-year period.
	</content>
</weather>


<weather>
    <title>BRIEF: Weather and Disaster Preparedness Day Saturday at the mall
	</title>
	<content>
		Mike Honigsberg, director of Enid and Garfield County Emergency Management, said the event is free and will include drawings throughout the event for NOAA weather radios.
		"Come see us and many other responders that work hard to protect and serve you all," he said. "There will be a static display of emergency vehicles and inside we'll have several organizations represented. So come out and talk to us."
		With severe weather season under way, Weather and Disaster Preparedness Day is a way for the public to get educated on what they need to do when severe weather strikes. The day also gives the public a chance to speak with a number of emergency response agency officials and ask questions.
	</content>
</weather>


<weather>
    <title>Mayor declares weather disaster
	</title>
	<content>
		The disaster declaration was signed Monday by Mayor John Tyler Hammons after the area was hit with a blizzard last week.
		Disasters were also declared after ice storms hit the area in 2007 and 2008, Moore said.
		The declaration for the blizzard of 2009 will have no effect unless the president issues a disaster declaration for the state, which will likely be in the next two weeks if it happens, Moore said.
		Whether the presidential declaration is issued depends on the amount of damage statewide, said Jeff Smith, Muskogee County Emergency Management director. For the state declaration, damage would have to total about $4 million.
	</content>
</weather>


<weather>
    <title>Brace yourself for a scorcher: 2015 set to be warmest on record, warn climate scientists
	</title>
	<content>
		This interactive graphic above created by Nasa, shows how the Earth has changed over time (credit: Nasa)
		However, there are expectations that while 2015 will become the warmest year on record, much of that may be due to the unseasonable El Nino event rather than a rapid acceleration in climate change.
		Others have also expressed doubts over the reliability of global temperature data.
		In April, London-based think tank, the Global Warming Policy Foundation, announced it was launching an inquiry into the integrity of official surface temperature records.
	</content>
</weather>


<weather>
    <title>The strength and quality of climate perceptions
	</title>
	<content>
		An organization's climate is a valuable resource for organizational effectiveness because it influences employees' commitment to the organization (e.g. [5] Carr et al. , 2003). However, research has shown that individual climate perceptions may vary among group members who share a similar environment (e.g. [14] Klein et al. , 2001). Employees may perceive their environment differently because they "draw on what they experience as their own backgrounds, their 'selves' when making sense of organizational events" ([20] Peterson and Smith, 2000, p. 110). Additionally, employees may develop different climate perceptions in weak organizational environments. In weak, as opposed to strong, organizational environments, there are ambiguous organizational values and few behavioral norms (e.g. [17] Mischel, 1977), which allows for individual differences in expectations and perceptions. The extent to which group members differ in their climate perceptions has been referred to as climate strength.
	</content>
</weather>


<weather>
    <title>Dramatic Climate Change Is Unpredictable
	</title>
	<content>
		The fear that global temperature can change very quickly and cause dramatic climate changes that may have a disastrous impact on many countries and populations is great around the world. But what causes climate change and is it possible to predict future climate change? New research from the Niels Bohr Institute at the University of Copenhagen shows that it may be due to an accumulation of different chaotic influences and as a result would be difficult to predict. The results have just been published in Geophysical Research Letters.
	</content>
</weather>